Jan Karon papers MSS 16077
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
- Memorabilia, Artifacts & Miscellany
  - Esmont House Party photographs (3 of 4 disks), 2008 September 27; 1 items CD (Othertype Disk 2494-003)
  - Esmont House Party photographs (4 of 4 disks), 2008 September 27; 1 items CD (Othertype Disk 2494-004)
  - "At Home in Mitford," a musical based on the novel by Jan Karon, Song Demos, 2009 February 5; 1 items CD (Othertype Disk 2495-000)
  - "At Home in Mitford," a musical based on the novel by Jan Karon, Complete Show, Act One, 2009 June 26; 1 items CD (Othertype Disk 2496-001)
  - "At Home in Mitford," a musical based on the novel by Jan Karon, Complete Show, Act Two, 2009 June 26; 1 items CD (Othertype Disk 2496-002)
  - Travel to Ireland, [2012]; 1 items CD (Othertype Disk 2497-000)
  - Dooley Book ["Come Rain or Come Shine"], [Chapters] 1-12, 2014 December 14; 1 items CD-R (Othertype Disk 2498-000)
  - Manuscript, 2015 November; 1 items CD-RW (Othertype Disk 2499-000)
  - "Jeremy The Tale of an Honest Bunny" typescript, unrevised, typed from a hand-written manuscript, undated; 1 items 3.5 floppy disk (Othertype Disk 2500-000)
  - Esmont guest house and statuaries, undated; 1 items CD-R (Othertype Disk 2501-000)
  - Esmont Farm, Dalgliesh Gilpin Paxton Architects, undated; 1 items CD (Othertype Disk 2502-000)
  - "Light from Heaven" Viking regular and large print editions, undated; 1 items CD-R (Othertype Disk 2503-000)
  - "Miss Fannie’s Hat" A Memory Disk, undated; 1 items CD (Othertype Disk 2504-000)
  - John O’Donohue Celtic Wisdom, undated; 1 items CD-R (Othertype Disk 2505-000)
  - Research for In the Company of Others set in Ireland, audio, undated; 1 items CD-R (Othertype Disk 2506-000)
  - Hard Drive (internal), 2011 November 28; 1 items Maxtor DiamondMax Plus 9, 60GB ATA/133 HD (Box 119)
  - Hard Drive (internal), undated; 1 items Toshiba MK3018GAS (Box 120)
  - Penguin USA, Video Presentations, Hardcover Tape 1, 1995 December; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0602)
  - Friends of the Library Annual Luncheon, 1996 February 15; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0603)
  - Quail Ridge Book club, 1996 February; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0604)
  - “Today” Show, 1996 December 3; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0605)
  - Jan Karon on CBS This Morning, 1997 June 9; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0606)
  - Message to Mitford from Montrose, [California], “Merry Christmas from the Mitford Appreciation Society,”, 1997; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0607)
  - “Jan Karon Mitford Author, Answering the Call,” Hallmark Creative Conference, The Gem Theater, 1998 May 7-8; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0608)
  - Hallmark Plus Winter Buy Meeting, Mitford Open, 1998; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0609)
  - University of Virginia Architectural Class Field Trip with Ed Lay to Esmont, 2000 November 11; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0610)
  - Jan Karon on “Today” Show, 2001 April 11; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0611)
  - “Escape to Mitford with Ms. Jan Karon, Solemn Pontifical High Mass – Diocese of Quincy - (D.A.W.N.) Diocesan Annual Women’s Nexus”, 2001 April 28; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0612)
  - “At Home with Jan Karon,” Paladin Pictures, LLC, 2001; 1 Cassettes VHS, running time 24:41 (Othertype Videocassette 0613)
  - “Jan Karon Greeting” Paladin Pictures, LLC, [2001?]; 1 Cassettes VHS, running time 1:10 (Othertype Videocassette 0614)
  - “At Home with Jan Karon,” Paladin Pictures, LLC, Episode 2, Rough Cut, Version #1, 2002 November 7; 1 Cassettes VHS, 37:00 (Othertype Videocassette 0615)
  - “At Home with Jan Karon,” "In This Mountain" – Paperback Release, Episode 2, Paladin Pictures, LLC, [2003]; 1 Cassettes VHS, running time 31:45 (Othertype Videocassette 0616)
  - Penguin, "In This Mountain" (PB), produced by Spier, NY, TV commercial running time is 15 seconds, Sound Hound, Inc., 2003 March 18; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0617)
  - "Jan Karon," Producer Shannon Woodland, 2003 May 5; 1 Cassettes VHS – NTSC, 6:50 (Othertype Videocassette 0618)
  - Penguin advertising spots for the "Shepherds Abiding" paperback, Fall and Christmas, by agency Spier New York, running time on television :15 each season, 2004 August 17; 1 Cassettes (Othertype Videocassette 0619)
  - 700 Club “Live,” [Interview with Jan Karon?], Episode 337-04, 2004 December 2; 1 Cassettes VHS, 59:30 (Othertype Videocassette 0620)
  - Viking, "Light from Heaven" (HC), produced by Spier, NY, Music Version 1 and Music Version 2, TV commercial running time is 15 seconds, Sound Hound, Inc, 2005 August 5; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0621)
  - Jan Karon CBS Early Show, 2005 November 8; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0622)
  - University of North Carolina TV, North Carolina People with William Friday, Jan Karon, Episode 33626, 2006 December 22; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0623)
  - Esmont Farm Blessing, undated; 1 Cassettes (Othertype Videocassette 0624)
  - untitled VHS, sent by J. Crandall from Plano, Texas, undated; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0625)
  - “Romances, She Wrote” starring Jan Karon, Cupid Productions, in a handmade decorated case, undated; 1 Cassettes VHS (Othertype Videocassette 0626)
  - “Face to Face with Jan Karon,” edited master, undated; 1 Cassettes Betacam SP, TRT: 15:02 (Othertype Videocassette 0627)